Min Jung Lee

Position Master's Student

Graduate School of Artificial Intelligence

Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH)

CONTACT Information Computer Vision Laboratory

Office #302, Science Bldg.II, POSTECH, 77 Cheongam Rd, Nam-gu,

Pohang, Gyeongbuk, 37673, Republic of Korea

Mobile: (+82) 10 8010 8372 e-mail: minjlee@postech.ac.kr Homepage: blog

RESEARCH INTERESTS My research interests mainly focus on developing novel models and algorithms to address practical challenges in deploying artificial intelligence systems to various real-world applications. I am currently focused on the following topics:

- Computational photography: image restoration, image enhancement, camera ISP, burst photography.
- LLM-based video understanding: video summarization, video captioning, action anticipation, contextual understanding, leveraging LLM.

The application domains of interest encompass a broad range, including multi-modal learning (e.g., Vision-language, Visual QA, and image captioning) and LLM (e.g., fine-tuning LLM and prompt engineering).

EDUCATION

Pohang University of Science and Technology (POSTECH), Pohang, Korea

MS Student., Graduate School of Artificial Intelligence (GSAI) Sep 2022 - Aug 2024

- Advisor: Prof. Minsu Cho
- Cumulative GPA: 4.05/4.3 (97.5 / 100)

San Francisco State University (SFSU), California, U.S.

Exchange Student

Jan 2020 - May 2020

• Cumulative GPA: 4.0/4.0

Chung-Ang University (CAU), Seoul, Korea

B.S., School of Electrical and Electronics Engineering (EEE) Mar 2017 – Feb 2022

- Advisor: Prof. Chang Ha Lee
- Honors: Summa Cum Laude
- Cumulative GPA: 4.31/4.5 (98.10 / 100, Rank: 11 / 201)

Publications

Min Jung Lee, Dayoung Gong, Minsu Cho, "LLM-based Video Summarization," On-going.

Jungwoo Kim, **Min Jung Lee**, Suha Kwak, "Fine-Tuning Strategies for Weather Condition Shifts: A Comparative Analysis of Models Trained on Synthetic and Real Datasets," in *Annual Symposium of Korea Information Processing Society* (ASK), 2024

Sanghyun Kim*, **Min Jung Lee***, Woohyeok Kim, Deunsol Jung, Jaesung Rim, Sunghyun Cho, Minsu Cho, "Burst Image Super-Resolution with Base Frame Selection," in *Proceedings of the IEEE/CVF Conference on Computer Vision and Pattern Recognition* (CVPR) workshop, NTIRE, 2024.

Min Jung Lee, Jongmin Lee, Sanghyun Kim, Sunghyun Cho, Minsu Cho, "Base Frame Selection on Dynamically Exposed Burst," in *Image Processing and Image Understanding* (IPIU) 2024.

Min Jung Lee, Chi-hyoung Rhee, Chang Ha Lee, "HSVNet: Reconstructing HDR Image from a Single Exposure LDR Image with CNN," in *Applied Sciences*, vol. 12, no. 5, p.

2370, Feb. 2022, doi: 10.3390/app12052370...

RESEARCH PROJECTS Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Nov 2022 - Oct 2023

Non-uniformly exposed burst processing using robust base frame selector. (ISP Project)

Samsung Advanced Institute of Technology (SAIT)

Sep 2022 - Oct 2022

Burst image enhancement in an extremely degraded environment by noise, blur and shift.

Term projects in coursework

• Deep Learning (AIGS538): Convolutional block attention module with regularization [pdf] Spring semester 2023

• Computer Vision (AIGS539): Fine-tuning strategies for semantic segmentation models [pdf] Fall semester 2022

RESEARCH EXPERIENCE

Computer Vision lab. @ POSTECH

Sep 2022 - present

- A video summarization framework that utilizes a Large Language Model (LLM) to select the most relevant frames based on a comprehensive context summary
- A frame selection model for burst image enhancement considering image features and motion information
- Synthetic RAW burst dataset under capturing non-uniform exposure from public video benchmark using inverse camera ISP
- Real-world RAW burst dataset under capturing non-uniform exposure using dual-camera system

Visualization lab. @ CAU

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022

• An image enhancement network for reconstructing an HDR image from a single random exposure LDR image with U-net

Professional Activities

Teaching assistant

AI Trends (AIGS703C-01) @ POSTECH

Fall semester 2023

Instructor

POSCO AI expert training course @ POSTECH

June 2023 – July 2023

Engineering Experience

Projects

- \bullet An algorithm replacing the authentic fingerprints in images with the fake fingerprints using edge connect for biometrics security [pdf] June 2021 – Aug 2021
- A mobile application on Google Play Store "Food Timer" suggesting the ideal time for cooking depending on the kind of food to users

 Sep 2019 Nov 2019
- A mobile application and built an Arduino circuit system for booking seat system for the pregnant in public transportation [pdf]

 Aug 2019 Sep 2019

Honors and Awards

Dean's List with Department Honor Scholarship

 \bullet Top 1 in a department

Spring 2021

• Top 10% in a department

Spring 2019, Fall 2018, Spring 2018

COMMUNITY SERVICES

Student Worker @ SFSU

Jan 2020 – May 2020

• Affiliated to IEEC (International Education Exchange Council)

• Promoted information sessions and social events among international students.

Language

Korean(native), English(fluent)

SKILLS

Programming Languages: Python

S/W Packages: PyTorch

Referees

Available on request.